A Guide to the Virginia Secretary of Public Safety Director's Correspondence and Subject Files, 1971-1982 (bulk 1976-1981)
Library of Virginia
- Director's Correspondence and Subject Files, 1971-1982 (bulk 1976-1981). (Box 1-35.)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Haynesville Correctional Unit #17), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (James River Correctional Center), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Mecklenburg Correctional Center), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Nansemond Correctional Unit #3), 1978. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Natural Bridge Learning Center) [empty folder], undated. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (New Kent Correctional Unit #16), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Patrick Henry Correctional Unit #28) [empty folder], undated. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Pocahontas Correctional Unit #13), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Powhatan Correctional Center), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Pulaski Correctional Unit #1), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Rustburg Correctional Unit #9), 1978. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Smith Mountain Lake Correctional Unit #24), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Southampton Correctional Center) [empty folder], undated. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Southampton Correctional Center Receiving and Classification) [empty folder], undated. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Spring Street Work Release Unit), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Stafford Correctional Unit #21), 1978. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Staunton Correctional Center), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (St. Brides Correctional Center), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Tazewell Correctional Unit #31) [empty folder], undated. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Tidewater Correctional Unit #22), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Virginia Correctional Center for Women), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Virginia State Penitentiary), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (White Post Correctional Unit #7), 1978. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Wise Correctional Unit #18), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Woodbridge Correctinal Unit #6) [empty folder], undated. (Box 3)
  - Fire Services Commission [5 folders], 1976-1979. (Box 26)
  - Fire Services Commission: Appointments, 1979-1980. (Box 15)
  - Fire Services Training, 1977-1979. (Box 26)
  - Fire Services Training, 1979-1980. (Box 15)
  - Fire Services Training: Audit, 1979-1980. (Box 15)
  - Fire Services Training: Bulletins, 1979-1981. (Box 15)
  - Form 424: Corrections, Dept. of, 1977-1978. (Box 21)
  - Form 424: Criminal Justice Services Commission, 1977-1979. (Box 21)
  - Form 424: General (G.O. Form 16/DPB 16), 1973-1979. (Box 21)
  - Form 424: Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of, 1977-1979. (Box 21)
  - Form 424: Notification of Intent (Monthly Report on State Agency), 1977. (Box 21)
  - Form 424: Rehabilitative School Authority, 1977. (Box 21)
  - Form 424: State Police, 1977-1978. (Box 21)
  - Forms Management, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Fuel Assistance Program: Virginia, 1979-1980. (Box 2)
  - Fuel Conditioner (TECHNOL), 1978-1981. (Box 2)
  - Fuel Conditioners, 1978-1979. (Box 3)
  - General Assembly, 1976-1977. (Box 5)
  - General Assembly, 1977-1979. (Box 5)
  - General Assembly, 1978-1980. (Box 5)
  - General Assembly [empty folder], 1980. (Box 3)
  - General Assembly: Selected Acts, 1979. (Box 5)
  - General Fund Revenue Projections (1978-1984), 1977. (Box 6)
  - Godwin Years (Summing up), 1977. (Box 2)
  - G.O. Form Budget 18 (3-73), 1977. (Box 9)
  - Governor's 10-Year Planning Proposal, 1979. (Box 2)
  - Governor's Statement: Goals, Objectives and Policies, 1977. (Box 30)
  - GR 46-1 through GR 52-8, 1979. (Box 29)
  - GR 52-9 through GR 58-20, 1980. (Box 34)
  - GR 59-1 through GR 64-20, 1980. (Box 34)
  - GR 65-1 through GR 71-20, 1980. (Box 34)
  - GR 72-1 through GR 81-15, 1980-1981. (Box 29)
  - Grievance Procedure, 1977-1980. (Box 2)
  - House Bills: 1978 General Assembly, 1978. (Box 6)
  - House Bills: Recommendations to Governor, 1981. (Box 31)
  - House Bills: State Police Recommendations to Governor, undated. (Box 31)
  - House Document No. 8 (Study on Personnel Management within the Commonwealth of Virginia), 1978. (Box 30)
  - House Joint Resolution 17 (HJR 17): Medical Needs of Incarcerated Children and Adults, 1980-1981. (Box 21)
  - House Joint Resolution 89 (HJR 89): Subcommittee on Corrections System, 1980-1981. (Box 2)
  - House Joint Resolution 130 (HJR 130): Sheriffs' Salaries, 1978-1979. (Box 19)
  - House Joint Resolution 150 (HJR 150): Insurance, 1978. (Box 19)
  - House Joint Resolution 156 (HJR 156): Excess Property Management, 1979. (Box 19)
  - House Joint Resolution 160 (HJR 160): Youth Employment Program, 1979-1980. (Box 19)
  - House Joint Resolution 203 (HJR 203), 1978-1979. (Box 19)
  - House Joint Resolution 220 (HJR 220): Relates to Fire Services Commission, 1979. (Box 19)
  - House Joint Resolution 237 (HJR 237): JLARC Study, Federal Funds, 1979. (Box 19)
  - House Joint Resolution 259 (HJR 259): Medical, 1979. (Box 19)
  - House Joint Resolution 264 (HJR 264): Education and Human Resources, Special Education Facilities, 1979. (Box 19)
  - House Joint Resolution 269 (HJR 269): Interagency Prescription Team Agreements, 1977-1981. (Box 19)
  - House Joint Resolution 274 (HJR 274), 1979. (Box 19)
  - House Resolution 44 (HR 44): Supervisory Authority of Capitol Police, 1981. (Box 19)
  - House Resolution 90 (HR 90) and Senate 918 (S 918): Federal Legislation, SBA Loans, 1979. (Box 19)
  - House Resolution 4257 (HR 4257): Federal Bill, Victims of Crime, 1979. (Box 19)
  - House Resolution 6417 (HR 6417): Federal Surface Transportation Act, 1980. (Box 31)
  - House Resolution 6466 (HR 6466): Federal Amendment to Clean Air Act, 1980. (Box 31)
  - House Resolution 7020 (HR 7020) and Senate 1480 (S 1480): Federal Hazardous Waste Disposal, 1980. (Box 31)
  - Human Services Activities: Local Task Force for Organization of, 1979. (Box 31)
  - Hurst, Mrs. Edity A.: Calls to Cabinet, 1979. (Box 19)
  - Industries' Operations at Penitentary, 1976-1979. (Box 8)
  - Information Committee, State, 1976-1981. (Box 2)
  - Insurance, State Employee Liability, 1979. (Box 19)
  - Interagency Cooperation (RSA-DOC), 1978. (Box 33)
  - Investigations: Aircraft, 1978. (Box 4)
  - Investigations: Bristol City Jail (Albert Leonard), 1978-1979. (Box 4)
  - Investigations: Coal Fields, 1978. (Box 4)
  - Investigations: Organized Crime in Coal Industry, 1979. (Box 4)
  - Investigative Capabilities: Public Safety, 1973. (Box 4)
  - Issue Identification and Analysis, 1976-1978. (Box 19)
  - Jail Construction: Minimum Standards, 1976-1978. (Box 31)
  - Jail Renovation, 1976. (Box 31)
  - Jail Standards, 1978-1981. (Box 31)
  - Jail Standards Task Force, 1979-1980. (Box 31)
  - Jailing of Juveniles, Standards for the, 1977-1978. (Box 31)
  - James River Brands: Smithfield Ham Products Company, 1979. (Box 19)
  - James River Correctional Center, 1978-1979. (Box 8)
  - Jaycees, 1977-1980. (Box 19)
  - JAYCOR (Speed Identification System), 1979. (Box 19)
  - Jefferson Award Nominations, 1981. (Box 19)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Committee (JLARC), 1977-1980. (Box 2)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Committee (JLARC): Program Evaluation, Virginia Drug Abuse Control Programs, 1975. (Box 19)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Committee (JLARC): Reports, 1978-1980. (Box 19)
  - Joint Task Force to Establish Goals and Objectives in Law Enforcement and Corrections, 1976. (Box 26)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College: Member, Administration of Justice Advisory Board Committee, 1978-1979. (Box 2)
  - Juror and Witness Assistance Handbook, 1976. (Box 19)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of, 1976-1977. (Box 11)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Aid to Localities for Law Enforcement (Michie Commission Study), 1977. (Box 25)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Annual Report on Crime and the Justice System in Virginia, 1980. (Box 25)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Appeals, 1978. (Box 4)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Appropriations Committee Presentation [empty folder], 1979. (Box 25)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Consolidated Labs, 1977-1978. (Box 11)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Crime Control Act Fund Recommendations, 1979. (Box 7)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: General Correspondence, 1978. (Box 11)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: General Correspondence, 1979. (Box 25)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: General Correspondence, 1980. (Box 25)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Goals and Objectives, 1976-1978. (Box 25)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Grant Review, 1977. (Box 5)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Law Enforcement Communications Study, 1976-1977. (Box 25)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Law Enforcement Manpower Study, 1977. (Box 25)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Major Objectives Workplan (1980-1981), 1980. (Box 9)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Miscellaneous, 1972-1975. (Box 25)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Phase-Down, 1981. (Box 25)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Plan (1980), 1979. (Box 15)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Privacy and Security, 1975. (Box 26)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Report by MASD, 1978. (Box 26)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Report on Codes, Procedures and Practices Which May Lead to Overcrowding in Local Jails [empty folder], undated. (Box 25)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: State Crime Prevention Initiative, 1980. (Box 11)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Study by MASD, 1977-1979. (Box 25)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Urban Analysis Project, 1978. (Box 25)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Victim/Witness Protection, 1979. (Box 25)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of: Virginia Criminal Justice Multi-Year Plan, FY 1979 Update, 1979. (Box 13)
  - Juvenile Court-Public School State Task Force, 1976-1977. (Box 33)
  - Juvenile Court-Public School State Task Force, 1977-1978. (Box 28)
  - Juvenile Detention Facilities, 1976-1980. (Box 31)
  - Juvenile Detention Home: Lynchburg, 1977-1980. (Box 31)
  - Juvenile Justice and Delinquency Prevention Advisory Council: Appointments, 1977-1980. (Box 15)
  - Juvenile Justice and Delinquency Prevention Advisory Council: General Correspondence, 1976-1981. (Box 25)
  - Juvenile Justice System Definitions, 1977. (Box 5)
  - K, 1979. (Box 19)
  - Kepone, 1978-1979. (Box 19)
  - Kiwanis Project: J.E. Givens, 1979-1980. (Box 2)
  - Law Enforcement, 1978. (Box 30)
  - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration, 1976-1977. (Box 1)
  - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration, 1978. (Box 1)
  - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration, 1979. (Box 1)
  - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration: Newsletters, 1980-1981. (Box 19)
  - Leases, 1976-1980. (Box 28)
  - Legal Fees, 1978. (Box 28)
  - Legislation, 1981. (Box 31)
  - Legislation: Domestic Violence, 1979. (Box 1)
  - Legislation: Driving under Influence of Drugs, 1979. (Box 28)
  - Legislation: Executive Order #10, 1978. (Box 1)
  - Legislation: General, 1979-1981. (Box 28)
  - Legislation Tickle File, 1981-1982. (Box 31)
  - Legislative Implementation Report, 1979. (Box 1)
  - Legislative Implementation Report, 1980. (Box 28)
  - Legislative Proposals: 1977-1978 General Assembly Session, 1977-1978. (Box 9)
  - Leonard, Laurence, 1977. (Box 2)
  - License Plates: Blind vs Public Use (General), 1979-1980. (Box 28)
  - Local Government Advisory Council, 1978-1981. (Box 28)
  - Local Government Advisory Council: Executive Order #48, 1977-1981. (Box 1)
  - Local Government Officials Conferences, 1977-1981. (Box 1)
  - Louisa County: Green Springs, 1976-1980. (Box 8)
  - Lynchburg Juvenile Justice System: Lynchburg Study Report, 1977. (Box 31)
  - Lynchburg Youth Services, Inc., 1978. (Box 31)
  - Management, 1978. (Box 30)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development: Billing Study, 1977-1980. (Box 10)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development: Exit Report from Corrections Enterprises, 1977. (Box 10)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development: General, 1977-1980. (Box 10)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development: Inter-Agency ADP Plan, 1976-1980. (Box 10)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development: Inter-Agency Systems, 1977-1978. (Box 10)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development: Internal Service Fund Financial Reports, 1981. (Box 10)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development: Policies, 1977-1979. (Box 10)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development: Privacy/Protection Act, 1977-1980. (Box 10)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development: Systems Development, 1976-1980. (Box 10)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development: Training, 1977-1980. (Box 10)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development: Vendor Conferences, 1976-1977. (Box 10)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development: Working Capital Fund Financial Reports, 1981. (Box 10)
  - Management Manpower Assessment Survey (VCU), 1977. (Box 1)
  - Management Support Program, 1979. (Box 1)
  - Mandated Programs, 1976. (Box 9)
  - Manpower Utilization Plan, 1978-1981. (Box 28)
  - Marijuana Offenders, 1979. (Box 33)
  - Mark IV, 1978. (Box 30)
  - MASD/MISD Meetings, 1976-1978. (Box 32)
  - Medicaid, 1976-1979. (Box 1)
  - Meeting Facilities, 1979-1981. (Box 28)
  - Mental Health: General, 1978-1979. (Box 1)
  - Metric Conversion Information, 1979. (Box 1)
  - Michie Commission: Report to Commission on State Aid to Localities, 1977. (Box 1)
  - Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers, 1978. (Box 28)
  - Mileage Reports, 1979. (Box 19)
  - Mileage Reports, 1979-1981. (Box 19)
  - Mileage Reports, 1980-1981. (Box 28)
  - Militia and Police Subcommittee, 1976-1981. (Box 28)
  - Mini-Budget: Corrections (1981), 1980. (Box 9)
  - Mini-Budget: Public Safety Agencies (1980-1982), 1980-1981. (Box 9)
  - Mini-Budget: State Police (1981-1982), 1980. (Box 9)
  - M.I.S. Directors, 1976-1980. (Box 32)
  - M.I.S. Director's Meetings, 1977-1978. (Box 32)
  - M.I.S.D. Briefing to Cabinet, 1977. (Box 32)
  - Model General Assembly, 1981. (Box 28)
  - National Crime Control Workshop, 1979. (Box 8)
  - National Crime Information Center, 1973-1977. (Box 32)
  - National Crime Information Center: Computerized Criminal History Report, 1978. (Box 4)
  - National Governors' Association, 1977-1979. (Box 13)
  - National Governors' Association, 1977-1981. (Box 8)
  - National Governors' Association: Committee Assignments, 1977-1980. (Box 8)
  - National Governors' Association: Grants, 1979. (Box 28)
  - National Governor's Conference Task Force on Crime Reduction and Public Safety, 1976-1977. (Box 13)
  - National Secretaries Association, 1977-1978. (Box 13)
  - New Mexico Report, 1978-1981. (Box 28)
  - New Mexico Trip, 1980. (Box 28)
  - New River Valley Juvenile Detention Home, 1980. (Box 31)
  - Newport News Shipyard Strike, 1978-1979. (Box 8)
  - Newsletters, 1980-1981. (Box 19)
  - North Anna Anti-Nuclear Demonstration, 1979-1980. (Box 28)
  - North Carolina Trip, 1978-1979. (Box 8)
  - Northern Virginia Legislative Tour, 1981. (Box 28)
  - Northern Virginia Regional Juvenile Detention Commission, 1976-1978. (Box 31)
  - O, 1979. (Box 8)
  - Objectives: Major Agency, 1979. (Box 29)
  - Occupational Safety and Health Administration, 1978. (Box 8)
  - Occupational Safety and Health Administration, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Offender Employment Assistance Program, 1976-1977. (Box 8)
  - Office Furnishings Committee [empty folder], undated. (Box 3)
  - Office Furniture Advisory Committee: Corrections, 1979-1981. (Box 28)
  - Ombudsman Project, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Opportunities Industrialization Centers: W.F. Gilmore, Rep., 1977. (Box 8)
  - Paging Service: Office of Emergency Management Services, 1978. (Box 28)
  - Pendleton Project, 1977. (Box 3)
  - Pennsylvania's Safety Inspection Program: Motor Vehicle Inspection, 1981. (Box 28)
  - Personnel [empty folder], undated. (Box 8)
  - Personnel Act, 1977. (Box 23)
  - Personnel and Training, 1977-1978. (Box 8)
  - Personnel and Training, 1978-1980. (Box 8)
  - Personnel Communique, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Personnel Funding Report, 1977. (Box 9)
  - Personnel Management Advisory Committee, 1977. (Box 8)
  - Personnel Management Information System, 1977. (Box 32)
  - Personnel Management Study, 1976-1977. (Box 8)
  - Personnel Review, 1977-1979. (Box 30)
  - Personnel Transactions, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Personnel Transactions, 1977-1981. (Box 21)
  - Piedmont Geriatric Hospital, 1977-1980. (Box 8)
  - Pittsylvania County Jail: Staff/Personnel Study, 1980. (Box 31)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1977-1979. (Box 22)
  - Pocahontas Correctional Unit #13: Statement of Deficiencies and Plan of Correction, 1981. (Box 8)
  - Policy: General, 1976-1979. (Box 8)
  - Population Projections, 1976-1978. (Box 30)
  - Positions Established and Abolished, 1978-1979. (Box 8)
  - Prince William County: Funds for Juvenile Detention Facility, 1977-1979. (Box 31)
  - Prince William Facility, 1976-1979. (Box 31)
  - Printing Plants: Capitol Area, 1977-1978. (Box 8)
  - Procurement Law Study Report, 1980. (Box 23)
  - Program Development and Evaluation, Div. of, 1981. (Box 8)
  - Program Monitoring Task Force, Statewide, 1981. (Box 28)
  - Proposed Legislation, 1981. (Box 31)
  - Prosecutor's Management Information System (PROMIS) Grant, 1979-1980. (Box 5)
  - Public Safety, 1977-1978. (Box 32)
  - Public Safety: E.E.O., 1978. (Box 32)
  - Public Safety: Issue Analysis, 1976. (Box 32)
  - Public Safety Organizational Study, 1977-1978. (Box 32)
  - Public Safety, Sec. of: Administration Bills, 1980. (Box 24)
  - Public Safety, Sec. of: Administration Bills, 1981. (Box 21)
  - Public Safety, Sec. of: Administration Bills (Recommendations to the Governor) [3 folders], 1980. (Box 24)
  - Public Safety, Sec. of: Data Processing [empty folder], undated. (Box 32)
  - Public Safety, Sec. of: General, 1976-1977. (Box 32)
  - Public Safety, Sec. of: General Correspondence, 1976-1980. (Box 13)
  - Public Safety, Sec. of: General (United Way), 1977. (Box 32)
  - Public Safety Services, undated. (Box 32)
  - Purchases and Supply, Dept. of: General, 1977-1980. (Box 8)
  - Purchases and Supply, Div. of: Agency Procurement Manual, 1979. (Box 23)
  - Purchases and Supply, Div. of: Vendor Manual, 1980. (Box 23)
  - RADCO Planning District Commission, 1979. (Box 32)
  - Reading is Fundamental, 1978. (Box 23)
  - Real Property, 1978-1979. (Box 8)
  - Reappropriation (from Item 159 and Item 160), 1978. (Box 23)
  - Reciprocal Agreements, 1976. (Box 32)
  - Rehabilitative School Authority [2 folders], 1976-1978. (Box 16)
  - Rehabilitative School Authority [4 folders], 1976-1979. (Box 16)
  - Rehabilitative School Authority, 1977-1978. (Box 32)
  - Rehabilitative School Authority, 1977-1979. (Box 16)
  - Rehabilitative School Authority, 1978-1980. (Box 15)
  - Rehabilitative School Authority: Allegation about Anticapitalist Teaching, 1977. (Box 16)
  - Rehabilitative School Authority: Bureau of Education for the Handicapped Review Team, 1980. (Box 15)
  - Rehabilitative School Authority: Investigation, 1977. (Box 16)
  - Rehabilitative School Authority: Master Plan (1980-1986), 1979. (Box 14)
  - Rehabilitative School Authority: Master Plan (1980-1986), Preliminary Draft, 1980. (Box 15)
  - Rehabilitative School Authority: Virginia Advisory Legislative Council Survey (Senator Wilder), 1977-1978. (Box 15)
  - Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of, 1979-1980. (Box 28)
  - Republican Governors Association, 1979. (Box 23)
  - Resource Mobilization Guide, 1978. (Box BOX)
  - Res'q Personnel Alarm System, 1978. (Box 23)
  - Review of the Report of the U.S. Regulatory Council, 1981. (Box 23)
  - Reynolds Metals Company Tour, 1977. (Box 23)
  - Right-to-Work Debate, 1980-1981. (Box 23)
  - Rules and Regulations Guidelines, 1979. (Box 23)
  - School Buses: General, 1977-1978. (Box 23)
  - Search, 1978. (Box 23)
  - Secretary Smith Briefing, 1976. (Box 32)
  - Senate 294 (S 294): Federal Proposed Legislation, 1981. (Box 23)
  - Senate 1245 (S 1245): Federal, 1977. (Box 23)
  - Senate 1373 (S 1373): Federal, 1979. (Box 23)
  - Senate 1393 (S 1393): Federal, 1978. (Box 23)
  - Senate 2720 (S 2720): Federal Public Transportation Act, 1980. (Box 23)
  - Senate Bill 13 (SB 13), 1978. (Box 23)
  - Senate Bill 28 (SB 28): Governor's Policies, Goals, and Objectives, 1978. (Box 23)
  - Senate Bill 139 (SB 139): Commonwealth Family Act, 1980. (Box 23)
  - Senate Bill 160 (SB 160): Local Option Meetings, 1978. (Box 23)
  - Senate Bill 196 (SB 196): Torte Claim, 1981. (Box 23)
  - Senate Bill 378 (SB 378): Privacy Protection Act of 1976, 1976-1978. (Box 23)
  - Senate Bill 402 (SB 402), 1978. (Box 23)
  - Senate Bill 437 (SB 437): Carried over to 1981 Mini-Session, Centralization of Architectural and Engineering Services, 1980. (Box 23)
  - Senate Bill 601 (SB 601): Establishment of Motor Vehicle Insurance Plan, 1979. (Box 23)
  - Senate Bill 601 (SB 601): Dudley Tax, Alcohol Beverage Commission, 1981. (Box 31)
  - Senate Bill 689 (SB 689), 1979. (Box 23)
  - Senate Bill 728 (SB 728): Good Time Laws, 1981. (Box 31)
  - Senate Bill (SB 765): Indeterminate Commitments, 1981. (Box 23)
  - Senate Bill 810 (SB 810), 1979. (Box 23)
  - Senate Bill 858 (SB 858), 1979. (Box 23)
  - Senate Bill 876 (SB 876), 1979. (Box 23)
  - Senate Bill 913 (SB 913): Marijuana, 1979. (Box 23)
  - Senate Bills (Recommendations to Governor), 1981. (Box 31)
  - Senate Finance Committee, 1977-1980. (Box 23)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 10 (SJR 10): Development of a Statewide Program for the Prevention of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, 1980-1981. (Box 28)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 31 (SJR 37): Air Pollution Study, 1978-1979. (Box 23)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 48 (SJR 48): Study of Virginia's Public Contracting Laws, 1980. (Box 23)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 51 (SJR 51): Establishment of State Crime Prevention Resource Center, 1978. (Box 13)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 52 (SJR 52) [2 folders], 1978. (Box 23)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 58 (SJR 58): Rehabilitative School Authority, 1978. (Box BOX)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 72 (SJR 72): Resident Trooper Program, 1978. (Box 22)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 88 (SJR 88): Insurance (self) for State Autos, 1977. (Box BOX)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 91 (SJR 91): Economic Productivity of Prison Population and on Work Release, 1980. (Box 22)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 93 (SJR 93): Crime Commission to Research Marijuana Laws, 1978. (Box BOX)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 96 (SJR 96): Implementation of Task Force, 1977. (Box 22)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 121 (SJR 121), 1977. (Box 22)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 155 (SJR 155): Regional Arson Investigational Units, 1979. (Box 2)